arkadium.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy

Data Privacy at Arkadium, Inc.

(the “Company”) has established a comprehensive privacy program, including a global privacy office and a chief privacy officer, designed to help us respect and protect your data privacy rights. This statement includes the Company’s European Union and U.S. Safe Harbor Privacy Statement and the Website Application Privacy Statement. 

U.S. - EU Safe Harbor Privacy Statement

For personal information of employees, consumers, healthcare professionals, medical research subjects and investigators, customers, investors, and government officials that the Company receives from the European Economic Area, the Company has committed to handling such personal information in accordance with the Safe Harbor Principles. 

Website Privacy Statement

Scope – this privacy policy covers only the Company’s websites and applications maintained by the Company. If you access the Company’s games or applications through a third party website, you may be required to also read and accept the third party website’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

The Company respects the privacy of visitors to its websites, as a result, we have developed this privacy policy. This privacy policy applies only to the operation of websites that directly link to this policy when you click on “privacy statement” in the website footer or within one of the Company’s applications. Through this website or platform the Company will collect information that can identify you, including, but not limited to your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other similar information that you provide the Company or is displayed on any social networking web (“Your Information”) when it is voluntarily submitted to us (however, see discussion below about “IP Addresses” if you have a broadband connection). We will use Your Information to respond to requests you may make of us, and from time to time, we may refer to Your Information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our websites, products and services. We may also use Your Information to contact you and/or provide you with general information as well as information about our products and services. We may also enhance or merge Your Information with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes. 

Information about You Received from a social network

When you use any Company game at a social network such as Facebook®, where our games are also referred to as “applications”, you allow the Company to access certain information from your profile for that site. The information you allow the Company to access varies by game and social network platform, and it is affected by the privacy settings you establish at the social network. You can control and find out more about these settings at the social network where you play our games. For example, the Company may access and store some or all of the following information, as allowed by you, the social network and your preferences: 

  * your first and last name
  * your profile picture or its URL
  * your user ID number, which is linked to publicly available information such as name and profile photo
  * the user ID numbers for your friends that are also connected to our game(s)
  * the login e-mail you provided to that social network when you registered
  * your physical location and that of your access devices
  * your gender
  * your birthday

By playing a Company game through a social network, you are authorizing the Company to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network could provide to the Company through the social networking website the Company’s application or game. Your agreement takes place when you "accept" or "allow" (or similar terms) one of our applications on a social networking site. 

Any other information transferred by you in connection with your visit to this site (“Other Information” - that is, information that cannot be used to identify you) may be included in databases owned and maintained by the Company or its agents. The Company retains all rights to these databases and the information contained in them. Other Information we collect may include your IP Address and other information gathered through our weblogs and cookies (see below). 

This site and application may use a technology known as **web beacons** \- sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow this site to collect **web log** information. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an e-mail message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered when you visit one of our websites by the computer that hosts our website (called a “webserver”). The webserver automatically recognizes some non-personal information, such as the date and time you visited our site, the pages you visited, the website you came from, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 7), and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL). We may also include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages in order to determine whether messages have been opened. 

This website may use a technology called a “ **cookie** ”. A cookie is a piece of information that our webserver sends to your computer (actually to your browser file) when you access a website. Then when you come back our site will detect whether you have one of our cookies on your computer. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately. For instance, our site may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the site. 

This website uses Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. Generally, an IP address changes each time you connect to the Internet (it is a “dynamic” address). Note, however, that if you have a broadband connection, depending on your individual circumstance, it is possible that your IP Address that we collect, or even perhaps a cookie we use, may contain information that could be deemed identifiable. This is because with some broadband connections your IP Address doesn’t change (it is “static”) and could be associated with your personal computer. We use your IP address to report aggregate information on use and to help improve the website. 

Areas of this website that collect Your Information use industry standard secure socket layer encryption (SSL); however, to take advantage of this your browser must support encryption protection (found in Internet Explorer release 3.0 and above). 

Subject to any restrictions of any third party platforms displaying the Company Applications, we may share Your Information with agents, contractors or partners of the Company in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for, or with, the Company. These agents, contractors or partners are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services for the Company, or services for the collaboration in which they and the Company are engaged (for example, some of our products are developed and marketed through joint agreements with other companies). We may, for example, provide your information to agents, contractors or partners for hosting our databases, for data processing services, or so that they can mail you information that you requested. 

The Company reserves the right to share Your Information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law. In exceptionally rare circumstances where national, state or company security is at issue (such as with the World Trade Center terrorist act in September, 2001), the Company reserves the right to share our entire database of visitors and customers with appropriate governmental authorities. 

We may also provide Your Information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this website or application to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat Your Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

In general, we collect, store and use your information to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. For example, we may use information collected from you in any one or more of the following ways: 

  * • to create and register your account and allow play of our games 
  * • to administer games and improve game play 
  * • for social networking purposes, including but not limited to identifying similar users
  * • to enable user-to-user communications 
  * • to provide technical support and respond to user inquiries 
  * • to prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service 
  * • to notify users of in-game updates 
  * • to provide in-game leader boards and promote in-game player achievements 
  * • to communicate about new and current games 
  * • to solicit input and feedback to improve the Company’s products and services and customize your user experience 
  * • to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems 
  * • to analyze trends and user traffic and gather statistical information 
  * • to inform users about new products or promotional offers 

One important use of your information is communication. If you have provided your e-mail address to the Company, we'll use it to respond to (i) customer support inquiries, and (ii) keep you informed of your in-game activity, including comments from friends, notifications about in-game status. [We may also send promotional e-mail messages and promotional SMS messages ("Promotional Communications") directly or in partnership with parties other than the Company.] 

You always have the choice to stop receiving Promotional Communications. When you receive Promotional Communications from us you will have the opportunity to "opt out" by (i) following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the Promotional Communication you receive or (ii) by editing your preferences. Please note that despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may still send you administrative messages regarding the Company games, including, for example, administrative confirmations, and notices of updates to our policies. 

From time to time the Company may offer Users the ability to enter sweepstakes and contest. This may be done in connection with the Company Applications or in connection with various third party independent sponsors. The official rules of such sweepstakes and contest are subject to the rules provided therewith, including but not limited to the collection of any additional information not contained in this Privacy Policy. 

As a convenience to our visitors, this website currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, data collection, and distribution policies. 

To be removed from our contact lists, please write to the Company at the following address: 

        Arkadium, Inc.
        920 Broadway, 2nd Floor
        New York, NY 10010
        Attn: Marten Engblom

Please note that you may continue to receive materials while we are updating our lists. 

We may update this website Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it, for your convenience, we will make the updated policy available on this page.
